Deepak Sinha

Portfolio

LinkedIn Profile

510-552-6667

deepaksinhahere@gmail.com

Summary

10+ years of web development with an interest to learn and focus on User Experience.

Skills

UI: Angular, React, Javascript, Node, HTML/CSS, Sass, MongoDB, GraphQL, Express

Tools: GitHub, VS Code, Version One, Jira, Agile, Figma, SAFe

Experience

Infoblox Inc., Santa Clara CA

Senior Software Engineer, GUI

December 2008 - November 2023

Cloud-based SaaS for network automation solution

2018-2023

- Developed in a framework using Angular, Sass, and Bootstrap.
- Scoped requirements, designed and implemented UI features.
- Collaborated with PMs and UX for workflows and wireframes.
- Used SAFe methodology for development.
- Worked on data visualization using D3.
- Worked with angular version 2, 7 and 12.
- Worked on improving accessibility of the UI.

NIOS – web user interface for network automation solution

2008-2017

- Responsible for the look and feel of the UI using HTML and CSS.
- Worked on technologies involving Wicket, Ext JS.
- Designed wireframes from requirements and developed common markup templates.
- Worked on several iterations and revamps of the UI.

Dextersoft, Fremont CA

Software Developer, Web

February 2008 – December 2008

TXU energy – self-service web portal

- Worked as part of a team to build the customer self-service web portal.
- Developed web pages from wireframes using HTML, CSS
- Resolved browser compatibility issues.

.....

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology from Mumbai university.

Took a **User Experience Design** course from General assembly in 2020. Took a **Full Stack Web development** bootcamp from UC Berkeley in 2023